RG 041:003, Connecticut Siting Council
Connecticut State Library
- Series 1. Hearing Transcripts, 1973-1992
  - Docket No. 105, Application of Connecticut Light & Power Company...for the reconstruction of the Stevenson-Newtown and Newtown-Plumtree 115-kv transmission lines through the towns of Monroe, Newtown and Bethel, Connecticut..., 1989 March 28 (Box 13)
  - Docket No. 107, An application of Metro Mobile CTS of Hartford, Inc....for cellular telephone antennas and associated equipment in the town of Bloomfield, Connecticut, 1989 April 3 (Box 13)
  - Docket No. 108, An application of the Connecticut Light and Power Company...for the construction of a 69-kv transmission line to interconnect the 14mw Southeastern Connecticut Regional Resources Recovery Authority Project of Preston, Connecticut, 1989 April 27 (Box 13)
  - Docket No. 109, Application of the Department of Transportation...for the construction of a telecommunications tower and associated equipment in the city of Hartford, Connecticut..., 1989 May 16 (Box 13)
  - Docket No. 111, Application of Waste Management, Inc. and Bio-Energy Partners for the construction of a 3.33 megawatt electric generating landfill gas management facility..., 1989 August 21 (Box 13)
  - Docket No. 112, An application of SNET Cellular, Inc...for a cellular telephone antenna and associated equipment in the town of Colchester, Connecticut, 1989 June 13 (Box 13)
  - Docket No. 113, Application of Metro Mobile CTS of Fairfield County, Inc...for cellular telephone antennas and associated equipment in the town of Ridgefield, Connecticut, 1989 June 12 (Box 13)
  - Docket No. 117, An application of Metro Mobile CTS of New Haven, Inc...for the construction, operation, and maintenance of a cellular telephone tower and associated equipment in the town of North Haven, Connecticut, 1989 November 1 (Box 13)
  - Docket No. 124, Application of SNET Cellular, Inc. of New Haven...for cellular tower and associated equipment in Lisbon, Connecticut, 1989 November 21 (Box 13)
  - Docket No. 125, Application of Metro Mobile CTS of Hartford, Inc...for the construction, maintenance, and operation of cellular telephone antennas and associated equipment in the city of Middletown, Connecticut, 1990 January 8 (Box 13)
  - Docket No. 126, Application of Metro Mobile CTS of Hartford, Inc...for the construction, maintenance and operation of a cellular telephone tower and associated equipment in the city of Hartford, Connecticut, 1990 January 4 (Box 13)
  - Docket no. 129, An application of Metro Mobile CTS of Hartford, Inc...for the construction, maintenance and operation of a cellular telephone tower and associated equipment in the town of Manchester, Connecticut, 1989 December 28 (Box 13)
  - Docket No. 131, Application of Metro Mobile CTS of Hartford, Inc...for the construction, operation and maintenance of a cellular telephone tower and associated equipment in the town of West Hartford, Connecticut, 1989 December 21 (Box 13)
  - Docket No. 132, Application of Continental Cablevision to construct a community antenna television tower in the town of Hartland, Connecticut..., 1990 March 1 (Box 13)
  - Docket No. 135, Application of United Illuminating Company to construct one of two electric combustion turbines, one diesel engine generator and one associated 115 kV switchyard at its existing English Station in the city of New Haven, Connecticut, 1990 June 21 (Box 13)
  - Docket No. 136, Application of SNET Cellular, Inc...to construct, operate and maintain a cellular telephone tower, antenna and associated equipment in the town of Plainfield..., 1990 July 10 (Box 13)
  - Docket No. 137, Application of Metro Mobile CTS of Hartford, Inc... to construct, maintain and operate cellular facilities in the towns of East Hartford, South Windsor and Windsor, Connecticut..., 1990 August 15 (Box 13)
  - Docket No. 138, Application of SNET Cellular, Inc...for the construction, maintenance, and operation of the cellular facilities in the towns of Plymouth, Harwinton, Winchester, and New Milford, Connecticut..., 1990 August 27 (Box 13)
  - Docket No. 139, Application of Metro Mobile CTS of Hartford, Inc...for the construction, maintenance, and operation of cellular facilities in the towns of East Hartford, Enfield, and Wethersfield, Connecticut, 1990 November 19; 1991 June 10 (Box 13)
    There are two transcripts for November 19, 1990 because there were two sessions.
  - Docket No. 142, An application of Springwich Limited Partnership...for the construction, maintenance and operation of cellular telephone tower and associated equipment in the town of Pomfret, Connecticut, 1991 April 22 (Box 14)
  - Docket No. 144, Application of the Connecticut Light and Power Company...for the construction, maintenance and operation of a telecommunications tower in the town of Newtown, Connecticut, 1991 August 27 (Box 14)
    Includes 2 audio cassettes.
  - Docket No. 147, An application of Springwich Cellular Limited Partnership...for the construction of facilities to provide cellular service in the town of Clinton, Connecticut, 1992 February 19 (Box 14)
    Includes 3 audio cassettes.
  - Docket No. 154, An application of the Department of Public Safety, Division of State Police...for the construction, operation, and maintenance of a telecommunications facility located off Steep Road adjacent to Bradford Mountain in the town of Canaan, Connecticut, 1992 August 11; October 19; November 10 (Box 14)
  - A hearing concerning proposed substation and switchyard regulations noticed in the Connecticut Law Journal of September 11, 1979, 1980 April 18; 2 copies (Box 15)
  - A copy of the telecommunications systems hearing summary, 1979 May 30, 31 (Box 15)